Kettle and Idols
Now then, let's get to the main project of Kettle and Idol!
Please give a cute title call!
My 3 main elements
Yo!
Now, let's introduce the three elements that make up Kokumo-san.
This is the corner where you will be introduced.
Let's get to know more about our guest idols.
Now, please tell us about your three elements.
Yes, here are my three major asservers.
Jajan.
Okay, can you tell us the first to the third?
The first is sweets.
The second is games.
The third is sleep.
Okay, let's hear them one by one.
First, sweets.
Yes, that's right. I love gummy bears,
If you look in my bag, there are always gummy bears in it.
Idols like gummy bears, don't they?
Yes, they do. But I also often make my own gummy bears,
You make them yourself?
Yes, I do. Not at all.
That's a first for you, isn't it?
I would like to make them, but I think I have made them in the past,
There really were people who made their own?
Yes, I did. I've been making it with all kinds of juices and stuff,
I have gelatin at home,
I make them.
Gummy bears are made from gelatin and what?
Just gelatin and juice,
Can you make them?
You make your own favorite flavors.
Yes, that's right.
What kind of juice do you recommend?
Gakult gummies.
No way.
Meteor bottles?
They are so delicious,
I make them myself, so I find the hardness myself.
The Gaclet gummies that are a little hard are really good.
There are no hard Gaclet gummies, right?
But it is a little bit,
Have you ever given them to anyone else?
Like a member?
No, I don't have any members.
Who? Did someone at home eat it?
Yes, my family members have eaten it.
Please tell me your honest opinion.
It's really delicious.
No way.
I make it with all kinds of juices,
Calpis, for example.
But it's not like the stuff they sell,
It's not juicy,
But it's freshly made, so it tastes good.
That's for sure.
What is the best juice?
Calpis and Gakult are the best.
Do you really like meteor bottles?
They are really delicious.
Oh, yeah.
You make it,
You just eat it at home.
You're bringing it with you?
It will be gone in an instant.
They'll be gone in an instant.
With the gummies that are on the market now,
What is your favorite gummy bear?
The one I would definitely buy if I could find them,
I haven't seen any yet, but I'm not sure if they're on sale right now because they're only available for a limited time,
I'm not sure if they are on sale right now or not, but they are limited time only, and I haven't seen them yet, but they have a Kororo sugar cane flavor,
It tastes like cherries,
Cherry has a skin around it, you know.
It's a Kororo, so it's a reproduction of the original,
It's like eating real cherries,
It's like eating real cherries, and I love it.
No way! You can feel the skin of the cherries?
It's got a nice crunchy texture,
It's very tasty.
I've always wanted to try that.
It's really delicious.
They look delicious.
Do many of the members like gummy bears?
Some of the members do,
The most? Among the members.
I like them the most.
But recently, Ayaka Yasumoto started to bring gummy bears too,
I don't know why, suddenly.
She's handing them out to everyone.
If I was handing them out,
I was handing them out, and they were handing them out.
I was handing them out and everyone got hooked,
Everyone started carrying around candy.
Yasumoto-san, it's been a long time,
Yasumoto-san, now, aren't those gummies good? It was like, "Hey, Yasumoto-san, those gummy bears are really good, aren't they?
He was a bit addicted to them.
I actually made friends within StarPlaza through gummy bears,
I like Stapla gummies after all.
I like Staple Gummies,With Ruri from Ukka,
as gummy friends,
Gummi was in the side as a birthday present.
There is a main birthday present, but...
The main present is there, but there are gummy bears next to the main present.
It's in there.
As expected, a present with gummy bears at the center might be nice.
We like each other properly, with gummy bears on the side.
Yes, that's right.
Thank you very much.
The first element of Ms. Kunitomo's gift was sweets.
Does your personality change quite a bit? During the game.
I don't know. When I play with my friends...
This program was provided by Mr. Masahiro, Ms. Yuka, Mr. Obara, Ms. Kari, and the Military Police Inspector.
Thank you very much.